The only thing better than going to work is taking a shortcut, so I can get there even earlier.
A mime!
My, my, I need to go to the tanning salon.
Where'd I go?
Good riddance!
Hooray!
Encore!
Hey, that's me!
Hooray!
Wow!
It's like looking in a mirror!
Here, try this!
Not bad!
Here's a dime!
See you later!
Oh, you're still miming me, eh?
Everyone at the Krusty Krab will get a kick out of this!
Come on, walk this way!
Hiya, Squidward!
Check it out!
I found a mime!
Great!
I hope it's had its shots!
I'm going on my break!
Great!
Oh, you're still miming me, eh?
Everyone at the Krusty Krab will get a kick out of this!
Come on, walk this way!
Hiya, Squidward!
Check it out!
I found a mime!
Great!
I hope it's had its shots!
I'm going on my break!
Oh!
Hiya, Squidward!
I'll be in the kitchen cooking patties if you need me!
Oh, look!
A mime!
Uh, can I get a medium-krabby combo?
Yeah!
Oh, look!
A mime!
Uh, can I get a medium-krabby combo?
Yeah!
Oh, look!
A mime!
Uh, can I get a medium-krabby combo?
I'm not getting my food, am I?
I don't know why I come here.
Let's see!
She ordered a...
Hey, mime!
I can't read your mime writing!
SpongeBob!
Yes, Mr. Krabs?
Me most useless employee
has been replaced by an even uselesser employee.
Oh, he's not useless.
He's a mime!
I can see that.
Where in Neptune's name did he come from?
He followed me from the park after I gave him a dime.
Everyone knows!
You never give a mime a dime!
Good luck getting rid of him!
Oh, why would I want to get rid of him?
He's great!
Oh, you'll see.
But until then, I'm getting rid of you!
Don't come back until you lose the quiet clown!
Oh, okay.
Come on, mime.
Whoa!
Sure is drafty in here!
All right, that was fun, but you heard Mr. Krabs.
You can go now.
That's enough.
Okay, go away now.
Bad mime.
Go back to the park where you belong.
Good day.
Good day!
Hurry!
Come get lunchies!
Ow!
Meow!
Oh, finished already, Gary?
Whoa!
Gary, you sure are a betchimate today!
Leave this lamp-raise!
How did you get in here?
Bad mind!
Bad!
Good night, Gary!
That is you, right, Gary?
Meow!
Phew!
Huh?
Oh, that's a good one!
Dr. Krabs was right!
I can't get rid of this mime!
What am I gonna do?
Meow!
You're right!
I do need some help!
Oh, but who could help me with this?
Meow!
Really?
Him?
Well, desperate times and all that!
Thanks, Gary!
Hey, sorry I'm late!
Hey, where'd I go?
Meow!
Oh, that way?
Alright, thanks, Gary!
Yeah, yeah, what do you want?
Sweet, merciful Neptune!
Hi, Plankton, I need help!
What's that silent sap doing with you?
I found him in the park and I gave him a dime!
Everybody knows you never give a mime a dime!
Nice knowing you, pal!
Please, I need help getting rid of him!
Oh, why didn't you say so?
Perhaps something a tad less destructive?
Oh, fine.
Well, everybody also knows the best way to get rid of a mime...
...is to make it talk!
How are you gonna do that?
I'm gonna catch him!
Oh, okay!
And then...
Torture him!
Wait, what?
Oh!
Huh?
Alright.
Eat hot blazer!
It's up to me to make him talk!
But to catch a mime, I'll have to think like a mime!
I'm gonna catch a mime!
Sorry we got your miming license taken away!
I'm not!
Well, anyway, what are your future plans now that you're not a mime?
Well, we've finally broken!
I can't be a mime!
I'll just be a clown!
I liked him better when he was a mime!